viamagus.com 2017-12-24

# Privacy Policy | Viamagus

This Privacy Policy of viamagus.com is made effective immediately by Viamagus Technologies Private Limited (“Viamagus”). The terms “we” and “us” refers to Viamagus and its affiliates, and the term “you” refers to you, the user of the Website. 

**General**

This policy covers how we treat your information (including personal information) that we collect and receive, including information related to your visit or use (including past visits or use) of our websites, emails, platforms, mobile sites, applications, other products and/or services (“Site”). You should read this policy before using the Site. By using or accessing the Site, or any part of it, you agree and acknowledge that you have read and understood the policy and consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your information as described in this policy. You should not use or access the Site, or any part of it, if you do not agree with any portion of this policy. 

**Information that we collect**

When you use the Site or register with us, you will provide us with information including, without limitation, your demographic information, your business information, your customer information, your transaction information and your personal information. Further, during your access and use of the Site, we may learn and collect additional information from and about you. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, phone number, gender, age, billing or credit card information and that is not otherwise publicly available. The term information shall include personal information. 

When you use the Site, we may also collect and store additional information which may or may not be personally identifying to you or identifiable with other information collected. Such information includes, without limitation, your internet protocol address, browser types, domain name, type of operating system and other statistical data involving your use of the Site and/or our services. This information is collected passively using various technologies or may be provided by you through communications with us. 

**Cookies**

When you use the Site, we may store some information on your computer or other device used to access the Site. This information will be in the form of a “cookie” or similar file. Cookies are small pieces of information that gets stored on your computer or device when you access the Site. We use cookies to track your usage, trends on the usage, and to improve the Site and analyse and assess changes to, successes and failures of the Site. These cookies remember information about your usage of the Site and help you navigate the Site. We do not use cookies to spy on you or otherwise invade your privacy. 

**Other Monitoring Programs**

For security purposes and to ensure the availability of the Site, we may also use software programs and tools to monitor network traffic, to identify unauthorised attempts to upload or change information, or otherwise cause damage to the Site. 

**Customer Service**

We may also collect information when you interact with our customer service in order to assist you and to improve the operation of the Site. 

**Your Customer Information**

You use the Site for your past, present and prospective customers and business associates (or provide them access to the same) and this may provide us with access to their information (“Customer Information”). We shall accord your Customer Information the same levels of protection that is provided to your information pursuant to this policy. 

By using this Site, you represent and warrant to us that any and all Customer Information has been collected and shared with us in accordance with all applicable laws, rules and regulations, and do not violate any privacy or other rights of third parties. By using this Site, you acknowledge that we have no responsibility or obligation with respect to the legal compliance of your collection practices with respect to such information and that you have informed your customers and business associates that their information is being shared with us and about this policy. By using the Site, you agree to indemnify us, and all our officers, directors, shareholders, employees and agents, with respect to any claim, suit or liability (including attorney’s fees and related costs), arising from your Customer Information. 

**How we use your information**

This information that we collect is used to contact you, to administer your accounts, for research, and to improve the quality and your experience of the Site and develop our present and future products and services and provide information of these products and services to you. We will not sell, share or disclose your information with any third party without your consent, except as provided for in this policy. 

We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the Site, such as service announcements, administrative messages and information regarding existing and new services, without offering you the opportunity to opt out of receiving them. You may also provide us with access to information which is already publicly available, or becomes publicly available to us in the future. Further, we may also receive information about you from third parties independent of your use of the Site. You understand and acknowledge that any such information we may collect cannot be accorded the protections of this policy. This policy does not apply to the practices of other entities that we do not own or control, or to people that we does not employ or manage. 

**Storage and Destruction**

We shall store all information in accordance with standard market practices relating to storage of information and this may involve storage in servers and databases owned and maintained by us and/or our affiliates, agents or service providers. We may also retain the information once the purpose for which it is collected has been completed and the same may be retained and/or destroyed in accordance with standard market practices applicable to similar businesses. 

**Access and Protection of your Information**

You information that is provided to us or collected by us shall be protected in accordance with standard market practices applicable to similar businesses. You have a right to access, modify or correct any information provided to us by the use of the Site. If you update, modify or correct your information, we may continue to keep copies of your information prior to such update, modification or correction for uses provided for in this policy. You can request internal deletion of your prior information at any time by requesting us with specific details of the information that you wish to delete, and we shall endeavor to respond to your request in a timely manner. 

**Disclosure of Information**

We shall not rent, sell, share or disclose your information with non-affiliated companies or persons, except as provided in this policy or the applicable terms of use of the Site, or to provide you with the requested products and services on the Site, or when we have your consent, or under the following circumstances: 

| We provide the information to our trusted partners who work on our behalf or with us under confidentiality agreements. These partners may use your information to help us communicate with you about our Site and our other products and services;  
---|---  
| We provide the information to our advisors and consultants for billing, business, legal and taxation purposes;  
| We may disclose the information pursuant to law, court orders, requests or orders of Governmental authorities, or to exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims;  
| We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the safety of any person, violations of the applicable terms of use of the Site, or as otherwise required by law;  
| We believe it is necessary to disclose the information to enforce the applicable terms of use of the Site and/or reasonably necessary to protect our rights and property or our officers, directors, shareholders, employees or agents;  
| We share your information with third parties who we may be in discussions with for investments in or financing of our projects;  
| We transfer information about you if we are acquired by or merged with another company or transfer a part of our business to a third party. Any third party or resultant entity that receives your information pursuant to a merger, demerger or business transfer shall have the right to continue to use your information.  
| We may publish any testimonials that you have provided about the Site and such testimonials and other marketing, promotions and advertisements may include your information that you have provided to us. We shall ensure that your information in the testimonials are not directly attributable to you, unless we receive your consent for the promotion;  
| We may publish information as may be required to perform the services you have engaged us to perform.  
  
**Anonymised Data**

We may also use your information collected to create aggregate anonymised data. We shall ensure that such anonymised data will not be directly identifiable to you or to the information shared with us. We may use this anonymised data any purpose including for research, analytics, studying usage patterns and to improve our products and services and develop new offerings. By using this Site, you provide us the right to use your information to create anonymised data and use it for our business purposes. 

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

Amendments to this policy will be posted to this URL and will be effective when posted. Your continued use of this Site following the posting of any amendment, modification, or change shall constitute your acceptance of the amendment. This policy may also be modified by the terms and conditions of the specific product or service of the Site that you are using. We request you to check the applicable terms and conditions of the Site to ascertain if any additional considerations are involved with regard to your information. 

**Questions and Suggestions**

If you have questions, suggestions, or require to contact us as per these Terms of Service, or wish to make a complaint, please contact us at: [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)
